mobilerated.com 2010-04-20

# Privacy Policy

September 09 2009

**Introduction**

This document describes our privacy policy, and outlines the types of personal data we may collect from those who visit our websites.

**Information we collect and how we use it:**

Many of our services do not require you to register for an account or to provide us with any personal information. However, to provide a full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

  * **Information you provide** \- When you register, we ask for personal information such as your name, email address, and account id/password. Depending upon the type of account, we may ask for more detailed information such as physical address, bank details, and other personal information. We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Kalador services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. We may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.
  * **Cookies** \- When you visit Kalador websites, we may send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We may use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences and tracking user trends, such as which games people like. You can set your browser to refuse all cookies, however, some Kalador features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.
  * **Log information** \- When you use Kalador services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit our website.
  * **User communications** \- When you send email or other communications to Kalador, we may retain those communications in order to respond to your requests and improve our services.
  * **Affiliated sites** \- Some services may be offered in junction with 3rd party websites. Personal information you provide to those sites may be sent to Kalador in order to process the service. We process that information as per this privacy policy.
  * **Links** \- Kalador may track your usage of links off our our website, to improve our services, advertising, and accountability of link usage.
  * **Other sites** \- This policy is for Kalador websites only. Kalador does not control over sites you may access from a Kalador website. Those sites may collect or solicit personal information from you.

In addition to the uses outlines above, Kalador may use personal information to:

  * Provide our products and services to users, including customizing content.
  * Audit, research, and analyse use of our services
  * Ensure the technical functioning of our websites
  * Develop new services and offer new products
  * Comply with laws or regulations

Information collected by Kalador may be shared with select third parties with whom Kalador does business, including suppliers, partners and customers.
